scientificblogging.com 2019-04-03

# 

## Science 2.0 - Privacy Policy

#### (Last Updated: November June 17, 2012)

At ION Publications LLC ("Science 2.0","Scientific Blogging", "Science20.com", "we," or "us"), we are committed to ensuring the privacy of our users. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes how personal information is collected from users of the Science 2.0 Web site located at dev2.science20.org ("Site"), and how that information is used and disclosed. By using our Site, you consent to the terms of this Policy. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

#### What is Personal Information?

Personal information is information that specifically identifies an individual, such as a user's name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other account number, and information about that individual's activities when directly linked to that person such as information about his or her purchases or use of services. Personal information also includes demographic information such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies you. 

Personal information does not include "aggregate" information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of products, services or users from which individual user identities have been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data. Likewise, information about the products you purchase may be collected and combined with information about the products purchased by others. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and user needs so that we can better consider new products and services, and tailor existing products and services to user desires. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

#### Personal Information We Collect

You provide personal information to us in a number of ways when you visit our Site or use the various services and activities available on our Site. For example, you provide us with personal information when you:

  1. Register on the Site; 
  2. Participate in a survey, contest or sweepstakes on the Site; 
  3. Participate or make comments in any forums or other interactive areas of the Site; 
  4. Submit/post an article or comment to the Site and voluntarily include your name or other personal information (including, without limitation, any personally identifying photographs or images you submit/post); or 
  5. Contact us by email for any reason (such as to request customer service or provide us with your comments/feedback).

We collect your name and email address in this manner. If you request or apply for compensation from us for your articles, comments or other submissions to the Site, we will collect certain additional personal and demographic information from you (including, without limitation, your full legal name, address, date of birth and social security number). 

We also collect personal information from you if you submit a job application or resume to us via email. Personal information collected in this regard includes your name and email address, as well as other employment related information that you provide to us in the resume and/or application. 

When you visit our Site, some information is also automatically collected, such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system and browser type and the time and date of your visit. This information is collected through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer by a Web site to give you a unique identification. We also use cookies on our Site to keep track of services you have used, to record registration information regarding your login name and password, to ensure you do not repeatedly see advertisements, to record your user preferences and to keep you logged into the Site. We treat automatically collected information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the personally identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only. 

Additionally, we use, and allow third parties to use, Web beacons on the Site to monitor the effectiveness of advertising or for other legitimate purposes. Web beacons are small, graphic images on Web pages or Web-based documents or in email messages that allow us or third parties to monitor who is visiting the Site or if the email has be read. Web beacons collect the IP address of the computer that the Web beacon is sent to, the URL of the page the Web beacon comes from and the time it was viewed. Web beacons may be linked to your personal information. 

We may use third parties, called third-party ad servers or network advertisers, to deliver ads to you on our behalf. These third-party ad servers may use cookies, Web beacons or other technology to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our Site in order to use it to present advertisements that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice or whether you can opt out of having this information used by third-party ad servers to provide targeted ads, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp. 

#### How We Use the Information We Collect

In general, we use personal information to process your requests or transactions, provide you with products and services, and inform you about other products or services we think will be of interest. For example, we use the information we collect to: 

  * contact you for administrative purposes or provide you with customer service;
  * complete transactions requested by you or to verify that you have submitted an article or comment;
  * respond to any questions, problems or complaints, or request feedback;
  * organize the Site and its various services and activities to better serve you and customize or develop our products and services; and
  * send you emails or other communications containing information about products and services that you might find of interest.

Personal information provided on our Site may be linked together or merged with other personal information we obtain about you so that we may better understand your needs and inform you about our products or services and those of our business partners. In addition, if we receive personal information from third parties with whom we have business relationships, we may combine this information with the other personal information we maintain about you. In either case, this Policy governs this information. 

####  Disclosure of Information

We do not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy. We share personal information with third-party vendors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. These functions may include, for example, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and processing payment transactions. In all cases we limit the information shared with our third-party vendors to that which is necessary to carry out those functions. We are not responsible for any information you provide to these parties directly, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them. 

We also disclose personal information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply this Policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our users' rights, property or safety; to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, our Site; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay. 

In addition, information about our users, including personally identifiable information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing or sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of our business assets. 

####  Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site contains links to other Web sites. Links from our Site to other sites or content are provided for your convenience only, and we do not have control over the content or privacy and security practices and policies of such third parties or other sites. Any personal information you provide on linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information. 

#### Choice and Access

To opt-out of receiving communications from us, or to request access to or that we correct or delete your personal information, we provide you with the following options: 

  1. Follow the "Unsubscribe" instructions contained in the communication from us;
  2. Email us at [Privacy at Science 2.0](mailto:admin@Science20.com)
  3. Or write to us at the following address with your request:

ION Publications LLC   
705-2 East Bidwell Street #170   
Folsom, CA 95630 

If, in the future, if we decide to share personal information with any third parties for their own direct marketing purposes (or that of another third party), we will update this privacy policy to reflect such change and provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of such disclosure of your personal information.

Please note that opting out of receiving communications from us will not prevent you from receiving administrative communications, such as those concerning the operation of the Site or about an article or comment you have submitted. 

#### Children

We do not intend, and the Site is not designed, to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old, you should not register with or otherwise provide personal information to our Site. 

#### Security

We use reasonable security measures in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. We cannot, however, guarantee protection of all information against interception, misappropriation, misuse, or alteration, or that your information may be not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others. Furthermore, we have no control over the security of other sites you might visit, interact with or do business with. 

Information you provide through the Site is protected by an encryption technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to ensure privacy and security during transmission. Your registration information is accessible online only through the use of a password. To protect the confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of the Site by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused or otherwise misappropriated. 

####  Policy Changes

We will modify this Policy if our privacy practices materially change in the future. We will notify you of such changes only by posting the new policy on our Site and indicating at the top of the Policy the date it was last updated. We encourage you to review the Policy each time you visit our Site to see if it has been updated since your last visit to make sure you understand how personal information you provide will be used. 

####  Questions / Additional Information

If you have any questions about this Policy, or the practices of or your dealings with the Site, please contact us at the following address or email us at [Privacy at Science 2.0](mailto:privacy@Science20.com): 

ION Publications LLC Science 2.0  
10580 N. McCarran Blvd #115-334  
Reno, NV 89503  

##### © 2006-2012 ION Publications LLC
